[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1403_0201_gates",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1403_0201_d_00_Container_gates",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1403_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1403_0201_gates_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1403_0201_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1403_0201_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1403_0201_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1403_0201_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1403_0201_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1403_0201_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1403_0202_tincturequest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 50,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1403_0202_d_00_Container_tincturequest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1403_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1403_0202_tincturequest_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1403_0202_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1403_0202_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1403_0202_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1403_0202_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1403_0202_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1403_0202_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1416_0201_sabotage",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1416_0201_d_00_Container_sabotage",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1416_Warden",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1416_0201_sabotage_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1416_0201_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1416_0201_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1416_0201_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1416_0201_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1416_0201_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1416_0201_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1416_0202_foreman",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1416_0202_d_00_Container_foreman",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1416_Warden",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1416_0202_foreman_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1416_0202_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1416_0202_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1416_0202_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1416_0202_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1416_0202_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1416_0202_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1416_0301_northeast",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 57,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1416_0301_d_00_Container_northeast",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1403_SurvivalistA",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_09",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1416_0301_northeast_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1416_0301_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1416_0301_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1416_0301_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1416_0301_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1416_0301_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1416_0301_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0201_lights",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0201_d_00_Container_lights",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1418_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0201_lights_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1418_0201_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1418_0201_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1418_0201_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1418_0201_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1418_0201_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1418_0201_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0202_azuretears",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0202_d_00_Container_azuretears",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1418_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0202_azuretears_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1418_0202_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1418_0202_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1418_0202_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1418_0202_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1418_0202_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1418_0202_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1403_0203_blightpox",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 52,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1403_0203_d_00_Container_blightpox",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1403_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1403_0203_blightpox_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1403_0203_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1403_0203_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1403_0203_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1403_0203_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1403_0203_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1403_0203_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1403_0301_blightstrength",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1403_0301_d_00_Container_blightstrength",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1403_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1403_0301_blightstrength_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1403_0301_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1403_0301_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1403_0301_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1403_0301_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1403_0301_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1403_0301_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1403_0401_blightmigration",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1403_0401_d_00_Container_blightmigration",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1403_SurvivalistA",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_10",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1403_0401_blightmigration_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1403_0401_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1403_0401_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1403_0401_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1403_0401_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1403_0401_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1403_0401_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1403A_0301_GKW",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1403A_0301_d_00_Container_GKW",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1403_SurvivalistA",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_12",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1403A_0301_GKW_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1403A_0301_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1403A_0301_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1403A_0301_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1403A_0301_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1403A_0301_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1403A_0301_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1413_0201_spriggan",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1413_0201_d_00_Container_spriggan",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1413_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_14",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1413_0201_spriggan_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1413_0201_spriggan_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1413_0201_spriggan_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1413_0201_spriggan_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1413_0201_spriggan_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1413_0201_spriggan_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1413_0201_spriggan_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1414_0101_ToReekwater",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 54,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1414_0101_d_00_Container_ToReekwater",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0502_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_13",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1414_0101_ToReekwater_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1414_0101_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1414_0101_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1414_0101_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1414_0101_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1414_0101_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1414_0101_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0501_ClamorousVox",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_00_Containter_weaponwrapperquest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_1501_ClamorousVoxSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0501_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0501_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1420_0501_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1420_0501_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1420_0501_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1420_0501_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0502_CVOne",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_01_01_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete1",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_0502_CVOneSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0502_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0502_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0503_CVTwo",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_01_02_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_0503_CVTwoSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0503_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0503_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0504_CVThree",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_01_03_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete3",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_0504_CVThreeSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0504_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0504_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0505_CVFour",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_01_04_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete4",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_0505_CVFourSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0505_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0505_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0506_CVFive",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_02_01_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete1",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_0506_CVFiveSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0506_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0506_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0507_CVSix",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_02_02_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_0507_CVSixSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0507_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0507_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0508_CVSeven",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_02_03_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete3",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_0508_CVSevenSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0508_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0508_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0509_CVEight",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_02_04_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete4",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_0509_CVEightSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0509_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0509_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0201_Torrent",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_00_TorrentContainer_weaponwrapperquest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0201_TorrentSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0201_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0201_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1421_0201_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1421_0201_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1421_0201_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1421_0201_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0202_TorOne",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_01_01_weaponwrapperquest_TorOne",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0202_TorOneSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0202_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0202_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0203_TorTwo",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_01_02_weaponwrapperquest_TorTwo",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0203_TorTwoSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0203_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0203_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0204_TorThree",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_01_03_weaponwrapperquest_TorThree",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0204_TorThreeSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0204_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0204_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0205_TorFour",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_01_04_weaponwrapperquest_TorFour",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0205_TorFourSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0205_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0205_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0206_TorFive",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_02_01_weaponwrapperquest_TorFive",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0206_TorFiveSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0206_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0206_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0207_TorSix",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_02_02_weaponwrapperquest_TorSix",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0207_TorSixSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0207_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0207_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0208_TorSeven",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_02_03_weaponwrapperquest_TorSeven",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0208_TorSevenSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0208_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0208_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0209_TorEight",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_02_04_weaponwrapperquest_TorEight",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0209_TorEightSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0209_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0209_b_Description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0201_Reformation",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0201_d_00_container_Reformation",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0201_Reformation_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0201_Reformation_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0201_Reformation_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1419_0201_Reformation_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0201_Reformation_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0201_Reformation_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0201_Reformation_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0202_Reformation_metalsraw",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0202_d_00_container_Reformation_metalsraw",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0202_Reformation_metalsraw_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0202_Reformation_metalsraw_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0202_Reformation_metalsraw_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0202_Reformation_metalsraw_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0202_Reformation_metalsraw_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0202_Reformation_metalsraw_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0203_Reformation_essencebalanced",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0203_d_00_container_Reformation_essencebalanced",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0203_Reformation_essencebalanced_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0203_Reformation_essencebalanced_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0203_Reformation_essencebalanced_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0203_Reformation_essencebalanced_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0203_Reformation_essencebalanced_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0203_Reformation_essencebalanced_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0204_Reformation_polishpure",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0204_d_00_container_Reformation_polishpure",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0204_Reformation_polishpure_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0204_Reformation_polishpure_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0204_Reformation_polishpure_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0204_Reformation_polishpure_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0204_Reformation_polishpure_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0204_Reformation_polishpure_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0205_Reformation_wieldertested",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0205_d_00_container_Reformation_wieldertested",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0205_Reformation_wieldertested_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0205_Reformation_wieldertested_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0205_Reformation_wieldertested_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0205_Reformation_wieldertested_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0205_Reformation_wieldertested_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0205_Reformation_wieldertested_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0206_Reformation_bindingstight",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0206_d_00_container_Reformation_bindingstight",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0206_Reformation_bindingstight_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0206_Reformation_bindingstight_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0206_Reformation_bindingstight_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0206_Reformation_bindingstight_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0206_Reformation_bindingstight_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0206_Reformation_bindingstight_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0207_Reformation_firesstoked",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0207_d_00_container_Reformation_firesstoked",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0207_Reformation_firesstoked_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0207_Reformation_firesstoked_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0207_Reformation_firesstoked_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0207_Reformation_firesstoked_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0207_Reformation_firesstoked_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0207_Reformation_firesstoked_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0208_Reformation_hafthewn",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0208_d_00_container_Reformation_hafthewn",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0208_Reformation_hafthewn_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0208_Reformation_hafthewn_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0208_Reformation_hafthewn_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0208_Reformation_hafthewn_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0208_Reformation_hafthewn_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0208_Reformation_hafthewn_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0209_Reformation_gripsecured",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0209_d_00_container_Reformation_gripsecured",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0209_Reformation_gripsecured_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0209_Reformation_gripsecured_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0209_Reformation_gripsecured_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0209_Reformation_gripsecured_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0209_Reformation_gripsecured_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0209_Reformation_gripsecured_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0101_RD_00",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0101_RD_00_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0101_RD_00_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_00_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_00_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1418_0101_RD_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1418_0101_RD_00_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1418_0101_RD_00_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1418_0101_RD_00_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0102_RD_01",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0102_RD_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0102_RD_01_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_01_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_01_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0103_RD_02",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0103_RD_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0103_RD_02_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_02_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_02_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0104_RD_03",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0104_RD_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0104_RD_03_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_03_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_03_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0105_RD_04",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0105_RD_04_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0105_RD_04_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_04_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_04_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0106_RD_05",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0106_RD_05_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0106_RD_05_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_05_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_05_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0107_RD_06",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0107_RD_06_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0107_RD_06_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_06_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_06_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0108_RD_07",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0108_RD_07_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0108_RD_07_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_07_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_07_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0109_RD_08",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0109_RD_08_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0109_RD_08_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_08_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_08_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1401_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1401_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1402_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1402_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1403_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1403_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1404_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1404_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1405_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1405_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1406_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1406_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1407_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1407_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1408_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1408_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1409_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1409_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1410_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1410_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1401_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1401_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1402_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1402_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1403_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1403_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1404_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1404_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1405_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1405_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1406_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1406_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1407_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1407_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1408_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1408_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1409_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1409_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1410_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1410_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1401_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1401_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1402_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1402_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1403_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1403_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1404_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1404_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1405_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1405_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1406_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1406_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1407_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1407_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1408_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1408_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1409_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1409_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1410_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1410_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1461_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1461_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1462_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1462_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1463_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1463_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1464_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1464_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1465_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1465_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1466_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1466_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1467_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1467_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1468_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1468_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1469_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1469_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1470_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1470_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1461_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1461_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1462_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1462_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1463_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1463_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1464_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1464_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1465_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1465_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1466_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1466_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1467_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1467_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1468_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1468_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1469_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1469_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1470_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1470_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1461_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1461_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1462_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1462_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1463_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1463_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1464_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1464_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1465_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1465_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1466_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1466_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1467_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1467_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1468_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1468_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1469_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1469_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1470_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1470_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Spy_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Spy_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Poach_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Poach_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Control_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Control_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Spy_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Spy_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Poach_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Poach_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Control_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Control_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Spy_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Spy_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Poach_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Poach_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Control_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Control_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_H_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_14_H_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_H_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_14_H_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_H_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_14_H_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_EXP_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_14_EXP_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_EXP_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_14_EXP_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_EXP_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_14_EXP_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    }
]